Mahshid Roshandelpir

Authorized to work in the US for any employer as permanent resident

(714) 360-9095 mroshand@mywvm.wvm.edu 1235 Wildwood Ave, Apt 70, Sunnyvale, CA 94089

Summary

Mahshid has academic and hands-on experience in information technology engineering. Specifically, she is well experienced in computer software and hardware maintenance, internet operations, and web design. She has passed several courses related to IT engineering and management, computer software and hardware, web design and development, and computer networking.

Education

Web Developer Certificate

Mission College, Santa Clara, CA

Selected Courses:

Introduction to computer hardware and software (A+)

Introduction to computer science

Web design and development 1 and 2

JavaScript 1

Web animation

User experience, interface

Social media marketing

Python programming

Database management systems 1

BS in Information Technology Engineering

Azad University, North Tehran Branch, Tehran, Iran

Thesis: "A Survey of Smart Building Management Systems"

Selected Courses:

IT Fundamentals

IT Project Management & Control

IT Strategic Management

Scientific & Technical Presentation

Network+

Computer Networking 1&2 & Lab

Artificial Intelligence

Management Basics

Engineering Economics

Organizational Behavior Management

Entrepreneurship

Logic Circuits

Computer Architecture

Digital Electronics

Software Engineering 1&2

Operating Systems & Lab

Programming & Algorithm Design

Theory of Languages

Database Design & Lab

Computer Graphics

Multimedia Systems

Experience

IT Engineering Intern

Road, Housing & Urban Development Research Center, Tehran, Iran

- Data Entry
- Computer Software and Hardware Maintenance
- Internet Operations

Sep 2012 – May 2017

Jan 2021 – Jul 2022

GPA: 4.0 / 4.0

GPA: <u>16.53 / 20</u>

Jun 2015 - Sep 2015

Class Projects Sep 2012 – present

- Design sample web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Design responsive and interactive websites with forms, galleries, etc.
- Design a simple computer game with Adobe Animate
- Design a user interface for an airline with Figma and Adobe XD
- Design a database management scheme for a bookstore using SQL
- Design an online library with Rational Rose Enterprise
- Design dynamic graphics with OpenGL

Skills Software

Computer Maintenance, Operating Systems, Internet and Searching, Microsoft Office, ICDL, Data Entry, Accounting, Mobile Device Management, Social Media, Computer Graphics, OpenGL, Multimedia Builder, Python, SQL, Rational Rose Enterprise, Web Design and Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), VMWare Networking, Network+, Cisco Packet Tracer, Adobe Animate, Adobe XD, Figma

Hardware

Computer Maintenance, Computer Assembly, Networking